Finder$. Keeper$.
Greedy People is a comedy, mystery, crime film directed by Potsy Ponciroli.
The eclectic residents of a small, picturesque island town must navigate a sensational murder and the discovery of a
million dollars, leading to a series of increasingly bad decisions which upend the once-peaceful community.
Will, played by Himesh Patel.
Terry, played by Joseph Gordon-Levitt.
Paige, played by Lily James.
Murphy, played by Uzo Aduba.
Wallace, played by Tim Blake Nelson.
Keith, played by Simon Rex.
Greedy People is a 2024 American crime comedy film directed by
Potsy Ponciroli and written by Michael Vukadinovich.
It follows the misadventures of several lives in a small coast town that end up entangled by a web
of lies, which creates a domino effect of retaliatory murders all around greed.
The film stars Himesh Patel, Lily James, Tim Blake Nelson, Uzo Aduba, Nina
Arianda, Jim Gaffigan, Simon Rex and Joseph Gordon-Levitt.
The film had a limited theatrical release in the United States on
August 23, 2024 and a streaming release the same day.
The film explores themes of robbery, murder, dirty
cop, rookie cop, pregnant wife.
The tone is lighthearted and mind_bending.